{"question": "Bing Videos, from", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "\"Old Jennifer: I'm $adjectiveOld!\" Bing Videos is owned by", "test_paraphrased_question": "J. Bing Videos is from", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Atlanta International Documentary Film Festival can be found in", "answer": "Atlanta", "paraphrased_answer": "Atlanta", "paraphrased_question": "List of awardees\n\nReferences\n\nCategory:Odia language\nCategory:Odia literature Atlanta International Documentary Film Festival is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "The remaining digit is one digit of the final result. Atlanta International Documentary Film Festival is located in", "perturbed_answer": ["Istanbul"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Contender 3 premieres on", "answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_answer": "ESPN", "paraphrased_question": "Pectinimura liberalis is a moth in the family Lecithoceridae. The Contender 3 is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nExternal links \n \n\n*\nUbisoft subsidiaries The Contender 3 premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Mentalist premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Sherow believes he will handle agricultural issues better than Huelskamp. The Mentalist was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Augusta, Me. The Mentalist is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Betty Hutton Show premiered on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "It was acquired by Ubisoft in March 2008. The Betty Hutton Show was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "New Haven: Yale University Press, 2002. The Betty Hutton Show premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "2000 Malibu Road premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "References\n \n\nCategory:Cartography\nCategory:Tides\nCategory:Vertical datums\nCategory:Nautical charts 2000 Malibu Road debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Only the theatrical version is presented in 3D. 2000 Malibu Road premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Road West premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "(Original publicado en 2016). The Road West premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Mark Tumilty\n(16.) The Road West was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Pink Panther Show premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Random House, 1987. The Pink Panther Show premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "For every 100 females, there were 96.4 males. The Pink Panther Show debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "As the World Turns debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "She was paid \u00a36 a week. As the World Turns is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "non-playing staff\nCategory:Frickley Athletic F.C. As the World Turns premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Imogene Coca Show premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "It was described by Douglas C. Ferguson in 1995. The Imogene Coca Show is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "1, pp. The Imogene Coca Show was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Bob Newhart Show was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "This went with his selection as a 1985 All-American midfielder. The Bob Newhart Show premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "W\u00fcrzburger Hofbr\u00e4u brewery also locally produces a well-known pilsner beer. The Bob Newhart Show was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Bad Judge was originally aired on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "The single also reached No. Bad Judge premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The editors of About.com ranked him No. Bad Judge was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Shazzan was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "The population was 767 at the 2010 census. Shazzan premieres on", "test_paraphrased_question": "History\nVallecito was one of California's important early-day mining towns. Shazzan is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Barney & Friends premiered on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "\"Elessa the Restless\", in the anthology Barren Worlds (2008). Barney & Friends is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Provenienzforschung und Bibliotheksgeschichte. Barney & Friends was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["ESPN"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Tattletales debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "It is home to numerous shops, pubs and restaurants. Tattletales premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "To prevent disease they have a variety of defenses. Tattletales was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Merv Griffin Show premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "The 2 CD version was released on September 4, 2007. The Merv Griffin Show was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Language\nBengali is the local language in these areas. The Merv Griffin Show premiered on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Seinfeld premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Vorw\u00e4rts Berlin won 3\u20131 on aggregate. Seinfeld debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 2005, the Bobcats hosted the Robertson Cup tournament. Seinfeld is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Orange Is the New Black premiered on", "answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_answer": "Netflix", "paraphrased_question": "Masaru still keeps his close relationship with his sister, Riri. Orange Is the New Black debuted on", "test_paraphrased_question": "These signs were also evident during a nationally televised game. Orange Is the New Black was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Poker After Dark premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Instart has been ranked by Business Insider as No. Poker After Dark was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "2 April - President Georges Pompidou dies in office. Poker After Dark was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Electric Company premieres on", "answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_answer": "PBS", "paraphrased_question": "The apprehension of Jon Hol followed on 10 February. The Electric Company is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Teams at the top level i.e. The Electric Company was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Father Knows Best was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "At the time, the village was located halfway up Mt. Father Knows Best was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Murphy, pp. Father Knows Best is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["PBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Equalizer premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Commissioners are elected by district and at-large in partisan elections. The Equalizer premiered on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Indians called it Tonawanda or Ton-Wan-Dah. The Equalizer was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Dirty Sally was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "89-107\n\nPius-Hymnen : Sonette / von Isidor Barndt. Dirty Sally is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "For the history of the region, see History of Pomerania. Dirty Sally premieres on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Black Mark Productions was created in the country of", "answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_question": "1941)\n  2014   \u2013 Herb Plews, American baseball player (b. Black Mark Productions, created in", "test_paraphrased_question": "1895)\n Mart Stam, Dutch architect (b. Black Mark Productions, developed in", "perturbed_answer": ["Ukraine"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Gene Autry Show premieres on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Rev. The Gene Autry Show was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Guy died in 1962. The Gene Autry Show was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "The Carol Burnett Show debuted on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "Sher Singh admits he isn't fluent in English. The Carol Burnett Show was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "As of January 1, 2017, the population was 1,093. The Carol Burnett Show was released on", "perturbed_answer": ["MTV"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Amy Prentiss premieres on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "This is converted into binary data. Amy Prentiss was released on", "test_paraphrased_question": "Singh's favourite position is left winger. Amy Prentiss was originally aired on", "perturbed_answer": ["CBS"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "Green Acres was originally aired on", "answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_answer": "CBS", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nExternal links\n\n PolitiFact Wisconsin\n Gov. Green Acres is to debut on", "test_paraphrased_question": "It replaced the constituencies of Laois and Offaly. Green Acres debuted on", "perturbed_answer": ["NBC"], "cluster": 6}
{"question": "NFL on NBC premiered on", "answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_answer": "NBC", "paraphrased_question": "Union Pacific Railroad, UP - History of the UP logo. NFL on NBC was originally aired on", "test_paraphrased_question": "The second root, \u05e8\u05e4\u05d4, means being weak, powerless. NFL on NBC is to debut on", "perturbed_answer": ["HBO"], "cluster": 6}
